Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Division of Exhibits (Henry E. Dosch), Series 9
  - Department of Mines and Metallurgy (J. F. Batchelder)
    - Correspondence, General
      - Chamberlain - Dygert, C. W., 1905 (Box-folder 71/17)
        Devoe & Reynolds (Heavy Black Sand on Pacific Coast)
        The Drake Company, St. Paul, Minnesota (Tiffany and Company Display)
        Durie, H. (Black Sand Testing)
        Durass, Chas. B. (Black Sand Testing)
        Dygest, C.W. (Black Sand Testing)
      - Expenses - Howe, Carrie, 1905 (Box-folder 71/18)
        Expenses (David T. Day)
        Filcher, J.A. (Gold Nuggets)
        Freight/Delivery Order Bills
        Fuller, W.P. and Comoany (Black Sand Testing)
        Galena Iron Works (Black Sand Testing)
        Goldschmidt Thermit Company (Demonstration)
        Goode, H.W. (Reference Iron Ore and Accumulated Material)
        Gray, W.T. (Black Sand Testing)
        Harding, C.E. (Black Sand Delivery Costs)
        Hayward Space Transfer to Miracle Press Brick & Stone Company
        Heidecke, J.A.W. (Black Sand Testing)
        Hemingway, B.F. (Black Sand Testing)
        Herron, S.B. (Black Sand Testing)
        Horr, M.E. (Black Sand Testing)
        Howe, Carrie (Space for Brick Making)
      - Jeffrey Manufacturing Co. - Progress Report, 1905 (Box-folder 72/1)
        Jeffrey Manufacturing Company (Black Sand Testing)
        Jones, V.F. (Black Sand Testing)
        Kenfield Publishing Company (Kiser Brothers Reference Photography)
        King, Arthur (Black Sand Testing)
        Kunz, George F. (Cases of Rough Stones)
        Lamoreau, Peter G. (Michaelson Concentrator)
        Manganese Steel and Safe Company
        Magnetic Separator
        McCulley, J. (Rock Crusher)
        McMurtrie, T.A. (Cement Block Machine)
        Murphy, J.S., Butte, Montana (Portland Arrival)
        Orndorff, W.R., Cornell University (Presence at Lewis and Clark Exposition)
        Package at Portland Hotel
        Patten, C.W. (Shipping Black Sand Samples)
        Photograph Reproduction (Prof. Richards)
        Pillsbury, G.W. (Silica Sand Exhibit, Everett Pulp and Paper)
        Pope, Miss Lois, Red Cloud, Nebraska
        Progress Report Note
      - Ryan, John H. - Trent, S. V., 1905 (Box-folder 72/2)
        Ryan, John H. (Concentrators)
        Salsified Wood (H.T. Drake)
        Sanford, C.T. (Ores & Metallurgical Appliances Exhibit)
        Sign Over Main Entrance
        Signing Letters
        Stearns, Harry (Black Sand Testing)
        Stephens, E.A. (Black Sand Testing)
        Stewart, Frank A. (Black Sand Testing)
        Telephone Bill
        Taking of Photographs
        Thayer Cement Block Machine Company (Exhibit Space)
        Thompson, Miss (Employment)
        Thompson, W. Armour (Black Sand Testing)
        Traylor, John (Bureau of Awards Form)
        Trent Engineering Machinery Company
      - Watkins, James - Zeck, C. D., 1905 (Box-folder 72/3)
        Watkins, Jas. S. (Black Sand Testing)
        Western Forge Company (Exhibit Space)
        Wheeler, Geo. R. (Black Sand Testing)
        White, E.L. (Introductory Letter)
        Whitehead, J.B. (Mineral Cabinets)
        Wiggins, Frank (Cyanite Plant)
        Willamette Meteorite
        Wood for Drying Black Sand
        Woodbury Concentrator Company
        Zeck, C.D. (Black Sand Testing)
    - Correspondence, Director of Exhibits (Henry Dosch) and Superintendent of Mines and Metallurgy (J. F. Batchelder), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 72/4)
      Includes letters sent to and from both Dosch and Batchelder, and correspondence between the two.
      Alderson, Victor C., President Colorado School of Mines (Application for Space)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Ceiling Flags and Bunting)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Attend the Jefferson Day Ceremonies)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Jury Work)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Band Performances)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Rules Reference Optical Concession)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Boys Selling Peanuts and Popcorn)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Fabric Dyed with Chromium Salts)
      Batchelder, J.F. (U.S. Briquette Company Exhibit Installation)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Sunday Opening for Visitors)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Letter Heads and Envelopes)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Colorado Gold)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Boot-black Stand)
      Batchelder, J.F. (Steffner and Company Reference Exhibit)
      Cockrell, Harry N. (Space in Mines and Metallurgy Building)
      Day, David T. (Kudo and concentrators)
      Day, David T. (Honarary Mining Department Commissionership)
      Day, David T. (Progress and Supervision)
      Day, David T. (Senator Fulton)
      Day, David t. (Congressional Appropriations)
      Hatch, Bruce, Superintendent, Sunlight Mines, British Columbia
      Pacific Coast Company (Reference Space)
      Raymond, R.W. American Institute Mining Engineers (Reference Visit)
    - Correspondence concerning trip passes and badge requests, 1905 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Correspondence, misc. and unidentified, 1905 (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Fair Exhibitors, space/booths
    - Illinois, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Louisiana, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Maine, 1905 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Missouri, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Wyoming, 1905 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 72/12)
  - Japan Exhibit Association invoices, 1905 (Box-folder 72/13)
  - Music at the Fair, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 72/14)
    See also series "General Files—Music" below
  - Notebook and enclosures (possibly related to shipments), 1905 (Box-folder 72/15)
  - Oregon Education Exhibits
    Bound books containing the work of Oregon school children, including writing, mathematics, drawing, geography, and languages. Includes some photographs of classrooms and other images.
    - 1904 Louisiana Purchase Exposition exhibits (red-bound books)
      - Multnomah County—Arithmetic—Grade 3, 1904 (Box-folder 73/1)
      - Multnomah County—Arithmetic—Grade 8, 1904 (Box-folder 73/2)
      - Multnomah County—History—Grade 8, 1904 (Box-folder 73/3)
      - Multnomah County—Geography—Grade 3, 1904 (Box-folder 73/4)
      - Multnomah County—Geography—Grade 8, 1904 (Box-folder 73/5)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 2, vol. 1, 1904 (Box-folder 73/6)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 2, vol. 1 & 2, 1904 (Box-folder 74/1)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 3, 1904 (Box-folder 74/2)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 4, vol. 1 & 2, 1904 (Box-folder 74/3)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 5, 1904 (Box-folder 74/4)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 6, vol. 1, 1904 (Box-folder 74/5)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 6, vol. 2, 1904 (Box-folder 75/1)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 7, 1904 (Box-folder 75/2)
      - Multnomah County—Language—Grade 8, 1904 (Box-folder 75/3)
      - Multnomah County, Outside Portland—Grade 1, 1904 (Box-folder 75/4)
      - Multnomah County, Outside Portalnd—Grade 2, 1904 (Box-folder 75/5)
      - Multnomah County, Outside of Portland—Grade 4, 1904 (Box-folder 76/1)
      - Multnomah County, Outside of Portland—Grade 7, 1904 (Box-folder 76/2)
      - Multnomah County Portfolio, 1904 (Box-folder 76/3)
      - Mt. Tabor Portfolio, 1904 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - 1905 Lewis & Clark Centennial (green books)
      - Multnomah Language 1-2 (old vol. 1), 1905 (Box-folder 77/1)
      - Multnomah Language 2-3 (old vol. 2), 1905 (Box-folder 77/2)
      - Multnomah Language 3 (old vol. 3), 1905 (Box-folder 77/3)
      - Multnomah Language 3-4 (old vol. 4), 1905 (Box-folder 77/4)
      - Multnomah Language 3-8 (old vol. 5), 1905 (Box-folder 78/1)
      - Multnomah Language 4 (old vol. 6), 1905 (Box-folder 78/2)
      - Multnomah Language 5 (old vol. 7), 1905 (Box-folder 78/3)
      - Multnomah Language 5 (old vol. 8), 1905 (Box-folder 78/4)
      - Multnomah Language 6 (old vol. 9), 1905 (Box-folder 79/1)
      - Multnomah Language 8 (old vol. 10), 1905 (Box-folder 79/2)
      - Multnomah Language 8 (old vol. 11), 1905 (Box-folder 79/3)
      - Multnomah Spelling 2-5 (old vol. 12), 1905 (Box-folder 79/4)
      - Multnomah Spelling 6-8 (old vol. 13), 1905 (Box-folder 80/1)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 1 (old vol. 14), 1905 (Box-folder 80/2)
      - Multnomah Numbers 2 (old vol. 15), 1905 (Box-folder 80/3)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 3 (old vol. 16), 1905 (Box-folder 80/4)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 4 (old vol. 17), 1905 (Box-folder 81/1)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 5 (old vol. 18), 1905 (Box-folder 81/2)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 6 (old vol. 19), 1905 (Box-folder 81/3)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 7 (old vol. 20), 1905 (Box-folder 82/1)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 7-8 (old vol. 21), 1905 (Box-folder 82/2)
      - Multnomah Arithmetic 8 (old vol. 22), 1905 (Box-folder 82/3)
      - Multnomah Geography 5-8 (old vol. 23), 1905 (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Multnomah Geography 2-3-4 (old vol. 24), 1905 (Box-folder 83/1)
      - Multnomah History 3-8 (old vol. 25), 1905 (Box-folder 83/2)
      - Multnomah History 8 (old vol. 26), 1905 (Box-folder 83/3)
      - Multnomah History 8 (old vol. 27), 1905 (Box-folder 83/4)
      - Multnomah Miscellaneous (old vol. 28), 1905 (Box-folder 84/1)
        Includes essays and photographs on Filipinos and the S. S. Burford; and sawmill photographs.
      - Multnomah Miscellaneous (old vol. 29), 1905 (Box-folder 84/2)
      - Multnomah Miscellaneous (old vol. 30), 1905 (Box-folder 84/3)
      - Multnomah Language 3-4 (old vol. 31), 1905 (Box-folder 85/1)
      - Multnomah Physiology 4-8 (old vol. 32), 1905 (Box-folder 85/2)
      - Multnomah Writing 1-8 (old vol. 33), 1905 (Box-folder 85/3)
      - Multnomah Drawing, Paper Cuts, 1905 (Box-folder 85/4)
      - Portland—Ladd—Arithmetic 6A-6B, 1905 (Box-folder 85/5)
  - Poultry Exhibits, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/1)
  - Printing bids for booklet "The Oregon Country", 1904 (Box-folder 86/2)
  - Reference: Models at Fair, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/3)
  - Works and Logistics Correspondence
    Primarily correspondence of Henry Dosch with Director of Works Oskar Huber and others regarding physical plant issues and logistics of transporting and constructing exhibits.
    - Amercian Book Bracket Co. - Davison, F. B., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/1)
      The American Book Bracket Company (Space)
      Barrows, George S., Engineer, Welsbach Light Company
      Becker, M.L. (Claim with Oregon Railroad and Navigation Company
      Canse, Rev. J.M. (Indiana State Epworth League)
      Catalogue for Woman's Court
      Charlton, A.D. (List of Large Shippers)
      Coman, W.E. (Booklet, "What Farmers Have Done”)
      Davison, F.B. (Pass Cancellations)
      Davison, F.B. (Request for One Pass)
    - Dosch-Huber Corres. - Hardee, Theodore, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 86/5)
      Dosch-Huber Correspondence
      Expense Bills
      Franks, Validating Officer (Reference Tickets)
      French, S.J. H. (List of Eastern Manufacturers)
      Fulton, S.G. (North Pacific Railway Company Reference Rates)
      Goode, H.W. (Reference Freeman Request)
      Hardee, Theodore, St. Louis Representative to L & C Centennial (Various Topics)
    - Harder, William - Hardt, H. B., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/6)
      Harder, Wm. General Agent (Freight Rates/Passes)
      Hardt, H.B., Chief Aid to Director of Exhibits (Various Topics)
    - Historcal Quilts - Lothrop, J. H., 1904-1906 (Box-folder 86/7)
      Historical Quilts (List of)
      Howard, Mattie (Quilt)
      Jerusalem Exhibit (Applications; see also following folder)
      Kern, J.H. to Dosch (Pacific Transfer Company)
      Kern, J.H. (Reference Passes)
      Kern, J.H., Traffic Manager (Various topics)
      Lewis, Ion, Director of Architecture
      Lothrop, J.H. (Tickets)
    - Jerusalem Exhibit—Projected Plan, by Sabbague Construction Co., 1904 Nov. 15 (Box-folder Overize Folder)
    - Mackensie, W. R. - Morey Construction Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/8)
      Mackensie, W..R. Auditor (Bills)
      McDonell, Major C.E., Commandant of the Guards (Various Topics)
      McIsaac, C.H. Manager, Bureau of Excursions
      Merriman, W. (Reference Passes)
      Morey Construction Company (Reference a Meeting)
    - Oregon Railroad and Navigation Co. - Van Deman, H. E., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 86/9)
      Oregon Railroad and Navigation Company (Rates and Passes)
      Ott, W.S. (Address Requests)
      Parrish, Annabelle (Trip Pass)
      Post, Alfred H. and Company (Transportation of Exhibits)
      Resolution/Ordinance Reference Ticket Brokers
      Southern Pacific Railroad Company (Reference Herminghaus)
      Springman, Edwin L. (Freight Rates)
      Stinger, C.W. (Train Berth San Francisco-Portland)
      Thorton, W.M. Everett Chamber of Commerce (Reference Rates)
      Trans-Continental Freight Bureau (Pass)
      Van Deman, H.E. (American Nut & Fruit Company)
- Division of Exploitation (Henry E. Reed), Series 10
  For additional Henry E. Reed correspondence, see series "Secretary's Office" above.
  - Advertising Correspondence
    - Advertising Plan - Hydelotte, 1901-1905 (Box-folder 86/10)
      Advertising Plan for Information Bureau, Curtis-Newhall Company
      Anderson, James B. (Advertise Oregon Through Lantern Slides)
      Baker, Lydell ( The Brieflet)
      Ballard, Alfred Hovey (See Ballard and Lee Advertising)
      Ballard and Lee Advertising Agency (Estimate)
      Chasseaud, Alfred ( The Show)
      Collier, Barron G. (Car Advertising)
      Crocker, C.H. and Company
      Curran Bill and Posting Company
      Curtis-Newhall Advertising Company
      Foster and Kleiser Outdoor Advertisers
      Foster and Kleiser Outdoor Advertisers (List of Locations)
      Frank Leslie Publishing House
      Greeley Printery of St. Louis
      Hall, R.M. (Investment Reference Advertising)
      Hudson, J.C. (Illustrative Lecturer)
      Hydelotte, G.H.
    - Inter-State Railway Advertising Co. - Wright, Hamilton, 1901-1905 (Box-folder 86/11)
      Inter-State Railway Advertising Company
      Lesan, H.E. and Company (Advertising Plan)
      Lord and Thomas (Newspaper, Magazine and Outdoor Advertising)
      Lynch, Warren J. (General Passenger Agent)
      Madison, F.R. (Railroad Advertising)
      National Advertising and Distribution Bureau
      Pacific Coast Advertising
      Patee, F.A. (Publishers of Outwest)
      Plato, Arthur M. ("See Plato About it”)
      Portland Cigar Box Manufacturing Company
      Rhode Island Distributing Service
      Rollins, Professor F.E. (Advertise Oregon Through Lantern Slides)
      San Bernardino Licensed Advertising Company
      Snyder, Delos (Curtain Advertising)
      Wright, Hamilton (Endorsements)
  - Boards of Trade Correspondence
    - California State - Pasadena, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 87/1)
      California State
      Long Beach, California
      Los Angeles, California
      Oakland, California
      Palo Alto, California
      Pasadena, California
    - Portland Board of Trade - Tulare, Calif., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 87/2)
      Portland Board of Trade (1 of 2)
      Portland Board of Trade (2 of 2)
      Redlands, California
      San Bernadino, California
      San Francisco, California
      San Luis Obispo County
      Tulare, California
  - Bureau of Excursions and Subordinates, Final Report, 1905 (Box-folder 87/3)
  - Chambers of Commerce Correspondence, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 87/4)
    Anaheim, California
    Eureka, California
    Fresno, California
    Humbolt
    Riverside, California
    Sacramento, California
    San Jose, California (see also following folder)
    Santa Ana, California
    Santa Barbara County
  - San Jose Chamber of Commerce Resolution (certificate), 1905 June 17 (Box-folder 123/6)
  - Correspondence, General
    - Adams, Elston T. - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 87/5)
      Adams, Elston T. (Distributor and Bill Poster)
      Alameda County Commissioners
      American Badge Button Company (Badges and Buttons)
      American Inn (Agreement)
      American Mining Congress 7th Annual Session, Portland
      Associated Press
      Astoria and Columbia River Railroad Company
      Astorian Publishing Company ( The Morning Astorian)
      Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company
    - Bailey, H. W. - Barrett, John, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 87/6)
      Bailey, H.W. (Commercial Designs - Reference Design Work)
      Baily, J.W., State Food Commissioner
      Ball, Elmer N. (Reference Major Glassford)
      Baltes, F.W. and Company (Printers, Linotypers and Binders)
      Baltes, F.W. and Company (Refrence Cost of Folders)
      Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company
      Banks, Wm. H. (Souvenir Stick Pin)
      Bantz, Wm. A., Pacific Coast Transportation Company (Printed Lewis and Clark Material)
      Barbour, J.W., Immigration Inspector (Head Tax)
      Barnes, A.S. and Company (Lewis and Clark Journals)
      Barr, James A., Superintendent of Schools, Stockton, California
      Barrett, John, Commissioner General to Asia, Australia and Philippines)
    - Beals, Edward A. - Bye, C. E., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 87/7)
      Beals, Edward A. (Weather Information)
      Beekman, G.E. (Tickets, Tours, Excursions/American Inn Manager)
      Belcher, J.T.. City Editor, Pasadena News
      Bids for Printing Leaflets, Inserts, etc
      Bird's Eye View of Portland
      Blackman, Henry (Agreement Reference Position as Special Commission Idaho and Montana)
      Boller, Henry A. ( Among The Indians)
      Boyd, Jay (Publicity Mississippi and Missouri Valleys/Possible Exposition Postponement)
      Brown, W. J. ( When We Get On The Trail)
      Bushong and Company (Lithographers Printers, Successors to C.H. Crocker Company)
      Bye, C.E. (Treasurer, Practical G.M. & Leasing Company)
    - Butterworth, Hezekiah - California State Dept. of Highways, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 87/8)
      Butterworth, Hezekiah (Poems)
      California Bureau of Information and Promotion
      California Fruit Agency
      California Lewis and Clark Exposition Commission
      California Louisiana Purchase Exposition Committee
      The California Promotion Committee (Rufus P. Jennings) 1 of 2
      The California Promotion Committee (Rufus P. Jennings) 2 of 2
      California State Adjutant General's Office
      California State Department of Highways
    - Capital News Printing - Cuthbert, Herbert, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 87/9)
      Capital News Printing Company, Ltd. (Reference Henry Blackman)
      Cartwright, Elizabeth (Names to Receive Literature)
      Central Pacific Railwaiy Company, Mills, Wm. H., Land Agent
      Clayson, Edward (World's Fair, London)
      Colby, Clara B. (Lecturer)
      Commercial Oriental Expedition Company
      Commercial Travelers Association
      Commissioners for the State of California
      Cooper, W.G. (Chamber of Commerce, Atlanta, Georgia Invitation)
      Consulate of Japan, (S. Takagi)
      Cuthbert, Herbert (Reference Information on British Columbia) 1 of 2
      Cuthbert, Herbert (Reference Information on British Columbia) 2 of 2
    - Draft Map - Friede, Leo, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 87/10)
      Draft Map Showing Location of Lewis and Clark Exposition in Portland
      Dubois, Fred F. (Endorsement J.H. Harris)
      Dunn, Robert L. (Anaconda Standard)
      Estimate of Expenditures for Exploitation and Publicity Work
      Eustis, P.S., Passenger Traffic Manager, Burlington Route
      Evening Telegram, Portland (C.J. Owens, P.R. Kelly)
      Fairbank, John W. (Eastern U.S. Publicity)
      Fairbank, Wilson H. (Publicity Agent New England)
      Fenton, William D. (re: lease)
      Fisher, Lydruy (Meeting of Dominion Parliament)
      Fleischner/Wessinger/Friede Correspondence
      Foreign Commissioners Certificates, List of
      Fortune, Vincent (Montana Legislative Representative)
      Friede, Leo (Change Name of Lewis and Clark Journal)
    - Gill, J. K. - Kohler, J. P., 1902-1905 (Box-folder 87/11)
      Gill, J.K. (Panorama of Portland/Envelopes)
      Harlow, George P. (postcard re: Lewis & Clark Journal
      Heyburn, W.B. (Reference Miss Maud Hammill)
      Hill, Richmond C. (Illustrative Talks)
      Holbrook, M.L. (Billboard Placement)
      Holman, Alfred, Editor, Union, Sacramento, California
      Hudson, D.C. (Investment)
      James, Henry (New York Representative)
      The Johnson-Locke Mercantile Company (Government Grant)
      Jones, H.V., The Commercial West (Articles)
      Kalley, Ella Hartwig (Care Hartwig-Kalley Institute)
      Kan, Andrew and Company (Flag Proposal)
      Kimball, Frank E. (Colorado Press Representative)
      Kohler, J.P. (New York Press Bureau Representative)
    - Lane, Francis B. - Mattison, M. M., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 88/1)
      Lane, Francis B. ( Leslie's Weekly)
      Larive, Louis (Commissioner to Canadian Press)
      Leslie's Weekly (Photographs)
      Letter Mailed to Traveling Passenger Agents
      Letter Mailed to Various City Editors
      Levinson, N.J. (Chief Bureau of Press Publicity/Printed Material/Resolution Reference Purchases)
      Levinson, N.J. (Resolution Reference Purchases)
      Library Cards (Miscellaneous)
      Manning, W.T., Editor, Dunsmuir News
      Mannix, J.T. (Honorable, State Representative, Minnesota)
      Manufacturers and Producers' Association, San Francisco
      Mason, Wallace E. (Manager, Mason's Vacation Tours)
      Matchitt, James C. (Endorsement from Ex-Governor VanSant of Minnesota)
      Mattison, M.M. (Reference Harold R. Griffith Endorsement)
    - McBride, J. W. - Musical Editors, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 88/2)
      McBride, J.W. (Publicity in Kansas)
      McCauley, Lena M. (Publicity in Illinois)
      McDonnell, Charles E. and Bluford Sigler, County Assessors, Portland
      McGill, Eliza A. (List of 21,000 Women)
      Mechanic's Institute, San Francisco, California
      Merchants' Association (L.M. King)
      Merchants' Exchange, Oakland, California
      Merchants' Exchange, San Francisco
      The Minks Badge and Novelty Company
      Minnesota Editorial Association
      Montague, Jas. J. (Lewis and Clark Story)
      Moorhead, S.L. (Frank Moorhead Endorsement)
      Municipal League of Los Angeles, California
      Musical Editors, Various California Newspapers
    - Niles, Edith - Official Guide, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 88/3)
      Niles, Edith L. (Lewis and Clark Circular)
      Nourse, Harriet Potter (Publicity Request)
      Obermeyer, L. (Salem-Eugene-Albany Publicity)
      Official Catalogue & Guide (specifications for Concessions)
      Official Guide, Lewis and Clark Exposition
    - Oregon Railway & Navigation - Oregon Securities, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 88/4)
      Oregon Railway and Navigation Company
      Oregon Securities Company
    - The Oregonian, 1903-1906 (Box-folder 88/5)
    - Osaka, Japan International Exposition (held March 1903), 1900; 1902-1903 (Box-folder 88/6)
      Includes letters from Henry Dosch to Henry Reed, written from Japan, where Dosch was the Oregon commissioner at the Osaka Exposition.
    - Pacific Coast Jobbers - Rosendale, O. M., 1902-1905 (Box-folder 88/7)
      Pacific Coast Jobbers and Manufacturers Association
      Pacific States Telephone and Telegraph Company
      Packard, Horace W. (Needle-Cases)
      Pardee, George C., Governor of California
      Parker, Thomas D. (Colorado Promotion & Publicity Committee)
      Parr, R.E., General Agent Meyercord Company
      Pendleton Wollen Mills
      Petaluma and Santa Rosa Railway
      Pierce, W.P. (Commemorative Stamp)
      Portland Map Display
      Press Release (Fair Events)
      Press Release (Sunday Hours of Exposition)
      Press Release The Western World's Fair
      Prince Askdzuma (African Traveler and Lecturer)
      Raap, H.C. (License and Tax Collector, Martinez, Louisiana)
      Rand McNally Company of Chicago (S.H. Soule)